大家好我是小木头
Hello everyone, I am Xiaomu
在AI圈内
In the AI ​​circle
今天呢有两则蛮重要的消息
There are two very important news today
Anthropic
OpenAI分别发布了他们最新款的模型
OpenAI released their latest models separately
Opus 4.6以及GPT-5.3-Codex
Opus 4.6 and GPT-5.3-Codex
本期视频
This video
我们会来对这两款模型
We will compare these two models
做一番简要的了解
Get a brief understanding
在过去两年的时间
in the past two years
随着新模型不断的推出
With the continuous introduction of new models
大家慢慢也意识到
Everyone gradually realized
新模型往往在基准测试上的得分
New models tend to score better on benchmarks
总是越来越好
always getting better
新模型也意味着更强大的能力
New models also mean greater capabilities
那看来实在没有太多可以分享的
It seems like there really isn’t much to share.
那本期视频
Then this video
我就让这两款模型
I will let these two models
给大家表演一个节目吧
Let's put on a show for everyone
不如来编个程
Why don't you program it?
看看他们在任务执行上的效果
See how well they perform their tasks
速度究竟怎么样
What's the speed?
那现在就开始今天的分享吧
Then let’s start today’s sharing now